We are in the midst of a group chat Thursday.
We're talking about who is qualified to speak on behalf of your black community, okay?
All right, let's go to the phone lines.
You know who speaks for us?
We all speak for ourselves because some of these speakers,
Stephen A. Smith, Van Jones, or somebody ridiculous like the candy girl,
they don't speak for us.
Well, so that was actually the question.
Who speaks for your black community?
I think there's something to be said for, like, you don't want people, like, speaking for you.
But there are times when you're in spaces where there is,
just by nature of you being on a panel or you being interviewed,
that you are challenged with questions that relate to the community that you're a part of.
And you don't want to speak for everybody, but you do want to speak intelligently
about how these things can be related to your community.
And I think it's important to have the people that are in those positions
be people that have proven to at least have the chops, so to speak, to do so.
I don't think a corporation, I don't really think that they have the authority
to put people in play that speak for the community like that.
It's the people that determine who they consider to be valuable.
I mean, if the people were just not watching him and lowering them,
because all they care about is money.
I think that they are operating from a money aspect,
but the people have to operate from a, you know, you're representing us aspect.
And a lot of times folks just don't feel like that's a fight worth having.
We are, we are, we are.